justlikenew.in 2019-05-31

# Privacy | JustLikeNew

JustLikeNew Technologies Private Limited (hereafter “JLNTPL”) is committed to protecting the privacy of its visitors (hereafter the "Visitors, "you" or “your”) to our Internet world wide web site http://www.justlikenew.in/ (hereafter the “Website”) that links directly to this privacy policy about the protection of personal information online. We aim for the Website to be a safe and enjoyable environment for you.

This privacy policy (hereafter the "Policy") primarily describes:

__The information that JLNTPL collects through the Website, which is hosted and operated from India;

__The use and role of cookies and similar technologies on the Website; and

__The security measures JLNTPL has in place to protect the information that JLNTPL gathers through the Website.

This Policy does not govern JLNTPL’s collection of information through any website, or by any other means, other than through this Website, or the collection of information by any parent, or subsidiaries of JLNTPL ("Other Entities").

Visitors are encouraged to read this Policy before using the Website. By using the Website, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Policy and the Terms and Conditions of Use of the Website, available at www.justlikenew.in/terms. If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of this Policy and the Terms and Conditions of Use of the Website, please do not use the Website.

JLNTPL gathers two basic types of information through the Website: (i) "Personal Information," information from which an individual can be identified, and (ii) "Aggregate Information," from which an individual cannot be identified.

Personal Information. You are not ordinarily required to register or provide Personal Information in order to access the Website. JLNTPL collects Personal Information from you only when you voluntarily provide it to JLNTPL - for example, purchasing JLNTPL products online, in contacting JLNTPL through the Website, or exploring business opportunities with JLNTPL, answering surveys and polls, entering contests and similar promotions and signing up for email updates and announcements concerning JLNTPL’s products and special sales and promotions. Personal Information may include your contact information (such as your name, postal address, telephone numbers and/or email address). Your payment information, such as credit card number and expiration date ("Payment Information"), will be collected by the respective banks and/or third party payment gateway, if you wish to purchase any product or merchandise made available through the Website ("Transaction"). 

Aggregate Information. When you visit the Website, JLNTPL and the third parties with whom JLNTPL has contracted to provide services, may collect anonymous information from three sources: server log files, cookies, and pixel tags. 

Server Log Files. Your Internet Protocol (IP) address is an identifying number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider (ISP). This number is identified and logged automatically in JLNTPLs server log files whenever you visit the Website, along with the time(s) of your visit(s) and the page(s) that you visited. IP addresses of all Visitors are used by JLNTPL to calculate the Website usage levels, to help diagnose problems with the Websites servers, and to administer the Website. JLNTPL may also use IP addresses to communicate or to block access by Visitors who fail to comply with the Policy and/or the Terms and Conditions of Use of the Website. Collecting IP addresses is a standard practice followed on the Internet and is carried out automatically by many websites. 

Personal Information. You are not ordinarily required to register or provide Personal Information in order to access the Website. JLNTPL collects Personal Information from you only when you voluntarily provide it to JLNTPL - for example, purchasing JLNTPL products online, in contacting JLNTPL through the Website, or exploring business opportunities with JLNTPL, answering surveys and polls, entering contests and similar promotions and signing up for email updates and announcements concerning JLNTPL’s products and special sales and promotions. Personal Information may include your contact information (such as your name, postal address, telephone numbers and/or email address). Your payment information, such as credit card number and expiration date ("Payment Information"), will be collected by the respective banks and/or third party payment gateway, if you wish to purchase any product or merchandise made available through the Website ("Transaction") 

JLNTPL gathers two basic types of information through the Website: (i) "Personal Information," information from which an individual can be identified, and (ii) "Aggregate Information," from which an individual cannot be identified. 

Personal Information. You are not ordinarily required to register or provide Personal Information in order to access the Website. JLNTPL collects Personal Information from you only when you voluntarily provide it to JLNTPL - for example, purchasing JLNTPL products online, in contacting JLNTPL through the Website, or exploring business opportunities with JLNTPL, answering surveys and polls, entering contests and similar promotions and signing up for email updates and announcements concerning JLNTPL’s products and special sales and promotions. Personal Information may include your contact information (such as your name, postal address, telephone numbers and/or email address). Your payment information, such as credit card number and expiration date ("Payment Information"), will be collected by the respective banks and/or third party payment gateway, if you wish to purchase any product or merchandise made available through the Website ("Transaction"). 

Aggregate Information. When you visit the Website, JLNTPL and the third parties with whom JLNTPL has contracted to provide services, may collect anonymous information from three sources: server log files, cookies, and pixel tags. 

Server Log Files. Your Internet Protocol (IP) address is an identifying number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider (ISP). This number is identified and logged automatically in JLNTPLs server log files whenever you visit the Website, along with the time(s) of your visit(s) and the page(s) that you visited. IP addresses of all Visitors are used by JLNTPL to calculate the Website usage levels, to help diagnose problems with the Websites servers, and to administer the Website. JLNTPL may also use IP addresses to communicate or to block access by Visitors who fail to comply with the Policy and/or the Terms and Conditions of Use of the Website. Collecting IP addresses is a standard practice followed on the Internet and is carried out automatically by many websites. 

Personal Information. You are not ordinarily required to register or provide Personal Information in order to access the Website. JLNTPL collects Personal Information from you only when you voluntarily provide it to JLNTPL - for example, purchasing JLNTPL products online, in contacting JLNTPL through the Website, or exploring business opportunities with JLNTPL, answering surveys and polls, entering contests and similar promotions and signing up for email updates and announcements concerning JLNTPL’s products and special sales and promotions. Personal Information may include your contact information (such as your name, postal address, telephone numbers and/or email address). Your payment information, such as credit card number and expiration date ("Payment Information"), will be collected by the respective banks and/or third party payment gateway, if you wish to purchase any product or merchandise made available through the Website ("Transaction") 

JLNTPL gathers two basic types of information through the Website: (i) "Personal Information," information from which an individual can be identified, and (ii) "Aggregate Information," from which an individual cannot be identified.

Personal Information. You are not ordinarily required to register or provide Personal Information in order to access the Website. JLNTPL collects Personal Information from you only when you voluntarily provide it to JLNTPL - for example, purchasing JLNTPL products online, in contacting JLNTPL through the Website, or exploring business opportunities with JLNTPL, answering surveys and polls, entering contests and similar promotions and signing up for email updates and announcements concerning JLNTPL’s products and special sales and promotions. Personal Information may include your contact information (such as your name, postal address, telephone numbers and/or email address). Your payment information, such as credit card number and expiration date ("Payment Information"), will be collected by the respective banks and/or third party payment gateway, if you wish to purchase any product or merchandise made available through the Website ("Transaction"). 

Aggregate Information. When you visit the Website, JLNTPL and the third parties with whom JLNTPL has contracted to provide services, may collect anonymous information from three sources: server log files, cookies, and pixel tags. 

JLNTPL gathers two basic types of information through the Website: (i) "Personal Information," information from which an individual can be identified, and (ii) "Aggregate Information," from which an individual cannot be identified. 

Personal Information. You are not ordinarily required to register or provide Personal Information in order to access the Website. JLNTPL collects Personal Information from you only when you voluntarily provide it to JLNTPL - for example, purchasing JLNTPL products online, in contacting JLNTPL through the Website, or exploring business opportunities with JLNTPL, answering surveys and polls, entering contests and similar promotions and signing up for email updates and announcements concerning JLNTPL’s products and special sales and promotions. Personal Information may include your contact information (such as your name, postal address, telephone numbers and/or email address). Your payment information, such as credit card number and expiration date ("Payment Information"), will be collected by the respective banks and/or third party payment gateway, if you wish to purchase any product or merchandise made available through the Website ("Transaction"). 

Aggregate Information. When you visit the Website, JLNTPL and the third parties with whom JLNTPL has contracted to provide services, may collect anonymous information from three sources: server log files, cookies, and pixel tags. 

Server Log Files. Your Internet Protocol (IP) address is an identifying number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider (ISP). This number is identified and logged automatically in JLNTPLs server log files whenever you visit the Website, along with the time(s) of your visit(s) and the page(s) that you visited. IP addresses of all Visitors are used by JLNTPL to calculate the Website usage levels, to help diagnose problems with the Websites servers, and to administer the Website. JLNTPL may also use IP addresses to communicate or to block access by Visitors who fail to comply with the Policy and/or the Terms and Conditions of Use of the Website. Collecting IP addresses is a standard practice followed on the Internet and is carried out automatically by many websites. 

JLNTPL gathers two basic types of information through the Website: (i) "Personal Information," information from which an individual can be identified, and (ii) "Aggregate Information," from which an individual cannot be identified. 

Personal Information. You are not ordinarily required to register or provide Personal Information in order to access the Website. JLNTPL collects Personal Information from you only when you voluntarily provide it to JLNTPL - for example, purchasing JLNTPL products online, in contacting JLNTPL through the Website, or exploring business opportunities with JLNTPL, answering surveys and polls, entering contests and similar promotions and signing up for email updates and announcements concerning JLNTPL’s products and special sales and promotions. Personal Information may include your contact information (such as your name, postal address, telephone numbers and/or email address). Your payment information, such as credit card number and expiration date ("Payment Information"), will be collected by the respective banks and/or third party payment gateway, if you wish to purchase any product or merchandise made available through the Website ("Transaction"). 

Aggregate Information. When you visit the Website, JLNTPL and the third parties with whom JLNTPL has contracted to provide services, may collect anonymous information from three sources: server log files, cookies, and pixel tags. 

Server Log Files. Your Internet Protocol (IP) address is an identifying number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider (ISP). This number is identified and logged automatically in JLNTPLs server log files whenever you visit the Website, along with the time(s) of your visit(s) and the page(s) that you visited. IP addresses of all Visitors are used by JLNTPL to calculate the Website usage levels, to help diagnose problems with the Websites servers, and to administer the Website. JLNTPL may also use IP addresses to communicate or to block access by Visitors who fail to comply with the Policy and/or the Terms and Conditions of Use of the Website. Collecting IP addresses is a standard practice followed on the Internet and is carried out automatically by many websites. 

JLNTPL gathers two basic types of informatLorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Aliquam at porttitor sem. Aliquam erat volutpat. Donec placerat nisl magna, et faucibus arcu condimentum sed.Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Aliquam at porttitor sem. Aliquam erat volutpat. Donec placerat nisl magna, et faucibus arcu condimentum sed.ion through the Website: (i) "Personal Information," information from which an individual can be identified, and (ii) "Aggregate Information," from which an individual cannot be identified.
